Thank you for watching.
Thanks again and I'll be rooting for you too.
Hello! This time I'm joined by Rikako Sasaki of Angulum and Akeimamo of Tsubaki Factory,
This time we have Rikako Sasaki from Angeleum and Akeimamo from Tsubaki Factory.
I will be presenting this time with these two, so please bear with me until the end.
Project 2023 Summer City Circuit is currently being held,
What are the differences compared to the spring?
I think Tsubaki Factory has a lot of songs for each season,
I am very happy to sing summer songs in summer.
That's right. We have two new members in Angeleum,
They are accompanying us on this tour,
So there will be times when all 11 of us will be performing together,
I hope we will be able to create a new form of Angelem from this summer tour.
In between the tours, we will also be performing at events.
On August 13th, we, Angelem, performed at the Rockin' Japan Festival 2023.
Yay!
We had already finished the show on the day of this distribution,
We are not sure how it turned out yet, but we are very excited about it,
I don't know how it turned out yet, but I think we are giving a hot live performance,
But I think we are giving a hot live performance.
Tsubaki Factory will be holding the Summer Festival 2023 Burning Hot on August 24.
We have had many strategy meetings with everyone and are working hard for the live,
I hope that many people will come to see the show,
On September 27th, Yuuki It's My Life If you are just delusional, you can be free! on September 27th. These three songs are really different from each other in genre.
These three songs are really different genres,
I think that Tsubaki Factory has broadened its range once again,
I hope everyone is looking forward to it.
Please take a look at the video.
Please enjoy!
I wish I could have done it, but it's a little sad.
I can't wait to see you.
I can't wait to see you again
With a sigh of love
Hey, hey, what do you like about me?
Hey, hey, touch me
Hey, hey, hey, don't say it with wordsHey, hey, hey. Don't say the words.
Come a little closer.
Please, please, please, please.
Don't tease me. Just hold me.
Goddess of passion
Wrap me in your love, give me your love
It's free love. I'll hold you.
I don't know what to do.
Enjoy your new night.
🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이 Soundu Hodori
Bustance after being clothed in righteousness
I'll hold a maiden in my arms
I heard there's as many years as there's love
I've counted them all.
Hey, hey, hey, can you tell?
I love you more than ever
I wonder if you've noticed
Hey, hey, hey. Love's a little too bashed-up for me.
Can we do it again?
Okay.
Don't be mean to me, give me a hug
Goddess of passion
Wrap me in your love, give me your love
It's free love. I'll hold you.
I'm too busted.
I'm ready to enjoy a new night
I love you I love you I love you I love you
I love you At the beginning of everything
I love you I love you I love you
This is not a dream
I love you I love you
Don't be mean to me, just hold me
Time for love and beauty
From the bottom of my heart, look at me
I'll hold you while I'm behind youI'll hold you between the backs.
What will I do?
I forgive you for everything.
Don't be mean to me. Give me a hug.
To today, with an honest face
I'll embrace you with love, I'll embrace you with love, I'll embrace you with love
I'd rather not love you. I'd rather embrace you.
I'm going to enjoy this new night.
Thank you for watching.
With Rikako Sasaki of Angulum,
Rikako Sasaki of Angeleum and Maasa Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory are presenting "Halo! STE.
From here I would like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer at a quick pace.
Yes, I'll do my best. I will do my best.
Okay, let's go.
Happy 21st. I was invited to perform at your birthday event the other day.
So, what was the first thing on your mind when you were on stage together?
I want to dance with you.
What's the point of today's fashion and hair arrangement?
Linking up with Ms. Sasaki.
What are your remaining accomplishments for this summer?
I haven't been to the beach.
What do you like about yourself?
My favorite thing about myself is my muscles.
August 13th is the 7th anniversary of Tsubaki Factory.
What is your pledge for the 8th year?
To be in a position to make Tsubaki Factory more exciting.
Thank you very much.
I have a lot of things to say,
Then, let's be serious,
In a serious way.
It's your 7th anniversary since joining Tsubaki Factory, and it's been 8 years,
How are you feeling? How do you feel about it?
As I said before.
But really, as we go about our daily activities,
I think that the members of the groupI want to continue to work hard and do my best to keep up with the members.
I want to keep working hard, and I want to do my best so that I don't lose to them.
That's right.
But I think Api is used to being a member of Tsubaki's energetic group, so...
I'll ask one more question. Today's fashion and hair arrangement points! Why did I mention that?
Did anyone else notice the link-up with Ms. Sasaki? I don't know, but we actually matched our colors, black and white and yellow.
I don't wear white very often, but I was wearing white already.
I don't wear white very often, but I was already wearing white. I can't wear it on my bag. But I was actually wearing a link coordinate.
I don't think we had matching outfits. We are wearing slightly linked outfits today.
We will ask Ms. Sasaki some questions after the VTR.
Hello! Sta.
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't
I won't kiss you okay
Even you couldn't take it away from me
TUES-TUES PRIDE BRIDE NOW ON SALE
Oh Let's play Lovely music
Let's dance Discoloring till morning
TUES-TUES FUNKY FLASHING NOW ON SALE
Is it because of the summer or a dream?
Whose fault is it, Ochanover New single
Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer Now on Sale
matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha matcha
Zatcha zatcha zatcha zatcha zatcha zatcha Mahalo bar
Ochanover New Single
Ochanover Mahalo bar Ikaenover
Shekena Mood Believing Power
Ordinary but Forbidden Dan-Dan Jatcha Jatcha Ochanover New Single
Jatcha Jatcha Ochanover Shekenare now on sale
Shekenatenare
There's so much to choose from, so many to choose from, so many to choose from, I can't choose just one.
Pampaka pampaka pampaka all over the world Before that, Ochanover New single
End of the world
Hallo! Ste, I'd like to ask you a question next.
What is today's theme? Flowers.What is today's theme? Flowers.
What is your favorite thing to do this summer?
Somen. Last weekend you performed at the Dokkin Chapin Festival 2023. How do you stay in shape on stage under the blazing sun?
Sleep and hydration If you could be born again, what would you want to be? The sun.
It's been about 3 months since a new member joined the group. What kind of person do you want to be in Angerme?
A senior member who can lead everyone and create an environment where everyone can grow and develop.
Thank you very much. I have so many questions, but the one that really caught my attention was, "If I were to be reborn, it would be as the sun.
You've been saying that a lot since you joined us.
I've been saying it since I joined Angelem, but there was a time when my catchphrase was "I'm Kokoro Sasaki, I want to be the sun for everyone.
I want to be a person who can light up everyone like that.
The sun is the only meaning of the word "sun," isn't it?
I may not be able to become such a great existence, but if I am reborn, I would like to become the sun, just once, just for a moment.
I think it's really hot, but I'd like to be the sun.
From my point of view, you are the sun. I think you are the sun.
I thought it was very nice that you answered about how you are trying to be a part of Angstrom after 3 months since the new member joined the group.
I'm the top of the group in terms of position, so I hope I can lead the group in that aspect.
Of course, that's what I've always wanted to do, and I'd like to be a person who can make the group more exciting.
But I also want the younger members to be able to grow and develop, so I want to be myself without being bound by formality.
I don't want to say that directly to them, but I want them to be themselves.
I want them to be able to express themselves in various ways, and I hope that I can pass these things on to them.
I think that as you go through various activities, you will develop your own particular tastes, and I want you to express them when you can, rather than keeping them bottled up.
I hope that we can grow in that way.
Although we are in different groups, I hope I can continue to learn from your example in terms of gestures and expressions.
Thank you very much.
Halo! Stay tuned for more after this!
Halo! Project 25th anniversary special event!
Project 25th anniversary special project!
Tsunku♡ appeared on the stage to celebrate the 25th anniversary with the senior members of Hello! Project's 25th anniversary with the senior members!This time it's the second part!
Please have a look!
Here you go!
Hello! Project 25th Anniversary Discipleship Talk in Hello! Project 25th Anniversary Disciples vs.
Yay!Ta-da!
I'm so convinced that this is the end of all the interviews.
I knew I shouldn't have skipped the order tinkey!I was thinking, "I'm not going to skip order tinkey on this one.
I was already absolutely finished with it all the way to the beginning.
Project, we had newcomers' performances in a span of three months,
I remember being told that I could change in three months,
Even now, when I start something, I always keep in mind to do it for 3 months at least,
I still try to keep in mind that when I start something, I should definitely do it once for three months. I think these are very good words, and I feel that these words were very important in my life.
I am sure this is because a year is composed of three semesters.
That's for sure.
If I had 3 or 4 months, I could go swimming, for example,
I think that if I had 3 or 4 months to learn swimming, for example, I would be able to do butterfly just by attending a 2-week summer course every day. A child.
That's for sure.
So, I think that if they had just one semester, they would be able to do butterfly.
I think we were talking about that.
That's for sure.
Image, 40 days of summer vacation.
If I had 40 days, I think I would be 0.5 seconds faster in 100 meters or something.
I think he was doing Halo Pro without doing any club activities, so I was wondering if he didn't feel that club activities would make him faster,
I think that's what we were talking about.
That's what I was talking about.
At that time, I was determined to get praised three months later.
After each rehearsal, they would say, "This time, this part of who's doing better,
I would hear from them by name.
I could tell.
Yes, I know.
Yes, there are.
But quite often, I am not even mentioned by name.
Me too.
It's a personal name.
I understand.
I understand Sunkusan, too.
I didn't want to mention it because it would be bad for the other members,
But the three of us here today are very talented,
Their faces...To be honest, they are very demanding.So I know that you feel relieved if I praise them as you feel,I really do.It really is.
I might have stopped after a little bit.
That's all.
But I'm glad. I was happy with myself at that time,
I was thinking, "I'm not growing,
I thought, "I don't have room to grow anymore,
I wondered why I hadn't grown since the last time I was there, and I wondered why I hadn't grown since the last time I was there,
I wondered why I hadn't grown since the last time,
I'm glad to hear that. I'm glad to hear that.
I was looking to see if he was praising Rainer's otaru.
I was looking.
I was wondering if there was any element of praise.
But even there, I tried not to praise too much.
I thought it would make the other kids less excited.
This is a complicated situation.
I met Goto separately today,
Maki Goto, I'm sure she didn't get much praise either.
But I'm sure she had a singing part,
I thought I was giving credit back to the three of them for that.
I am glad.
But, as I said before, all three of them had moments of sudden growth,
There were several peaks,
You don't realize it.
When that happens, I'm happy for them.
I don't notice it. By myself.
Suzuki and Karin have been doing it since they were little,
I think they were praised unexpectedly at first.
Not only me.
Then, when a new member joined,
Everyone's eyes go that way,
There are times when you feel a little lonely.Yes, there is.It depends on whether or not you can grow up during that time,What happens after that depends on whether you can grow up during those times or not.
I think these three are a group of people who have overcome that.
I am happy for them.Oh, thank God!
I'm going to cry.
Now that I was hungry.
The singing has continued even after graduation,
Oda is also taking care of the younger students,
And his guidance is for his own benefit,
I'm going to cry.
Please continue to care about her.
I'm not sure if what I remember is a proper sentence, I was only 12 or something, so it's just a rough memory,
Just as Mickey Mouse will always be Mickey Mouse,
Just as Mickey Mouse is always Mickey Mouse, you guys should always be yourselves and be ready to go to work whenever you are called.
But I was told that it did not mean that I should wear proper makeup or dress properly,
I wondered what he meant by that.
Now I realize how difficult it is to maintain a mindset that is always ready to be out in the open,
In fact, I think you asked me something that is very difficult to put into words.
What I wanted to say was not to be a good singer, or to be coy,
I think he wanted me to be a professional.
Hmmm.
I don't want to bring my own mood into it, and I don't know what's going on in my private life, but let's be professional anyway.
So, as an example, Mickey welcomes you with a wave of his hand even in the hot, hot summer.
I wanted that image. I wanted them to have that feeling.
The feeling of not being thick.
Hmmm, I see.
I think everyone related to Halo Pro is doing their best, like the members who stay in their dressing rooms and don't come out.
Eh?
I haven't heard that much in the past.
That's right.
In the case of common entertainment stories, they don't come out of the dressing room, or they leave in the middle of an interview.
It's a real thing.
Hmmm.
You don't hear about that kind of thing much, do you?
Yes, I do.
I thought it was outrageous.But I feel that Tsunku III created such an environment,I don't know...it's not like we write the songs ourselves,I don't know...it's not like we write the songs ourselves,
We are performing songs that we have been given,
We are performing songs that were given to us, and it has become ingrained in us that we are not great at anything.
That's why,
It doesn't mean that we can hold back.
That's not what I mean,
It is a matter of course,
We should be grateful that we have an environment in which we can perform,
Such words during the geneproduction,
That is what we should be thankful for,
Even if those words didn't reach us in words,
I feel that because it was delivered to us, there was not so much of that.
Well, this was just the beginning.
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume,
I am sure that everyone is living in the same way,
I have respect for my seniors and respect for my juniors,
I think that respect for our seniors and respect for our juniors will lead us to the next stage.
If we have this, I think we will be connected.
I am not going to stop talking about it,
But that's all for now,
It's not enough!
I just stood at the entrance.
Really.
We are now in the midst of a special 25th anniversary dialogue.
Whenever there is an opportunity, I would like to do it again.
I'd like to do it. Once a month.
Once a month.
Yes, that's all I have to say,
Thank you very much for your time today, Mr. TsunkuⅮs.
I would like to ask for your continued support for Hello!
Bye bye!
I'm listening to a really great story.
Now only the music will end.That was already after Sayumo and I sang at the Super Arena.I haven't sung a single song by myself yet.
The ceiling is soooo high!Ceiling...
Wow!
Wait, I got surprised before the fourth place.
That's a thumbnail, totally!
Next is a presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
There are so many lyrics in the Hello! Project has many lyrics that really touched my heart,
Project, and I would like to share some of them with you.
I would like to present one of Tsubaki Factory's songs, "Kimi to Boku no Kizuna (Bond between you and me)",
In the chorus of the song, there is a part where Riko Yamagishi sings alone,
In the chorus, there is a part where Riko Yamagishi sings alone, "You're not alone,
Whenever I sing this song, my heart gets touched by it,
I feel that I am not alone, and I think about everyone who sings with me,
It reminds me of the people I sing with, my family, and Masamiki,
I love the lyrics because they remind me of everyone I sing with, my family around me, and Masamiki.
I love it too.
I am an alumni of Angeleum.
I am an alumni from the latest single,
I'm going to sing the second chorus as a soloist,
There is a lyric in the second chorus that says, "I wonder what I can do,
This song was Akari Takeuchi's last single,
This song was the last single of Ms. Takeuchi Akari, and we have been working together ever since we started working together under Ms. Takeuchi,
I've been working with her ever since I first discovered Angeleum under her leadership, and the moment she was chosen as the leader was also one of those moments,
We have welcomed many juniors and sent them off,
I have always wondered what I could do to be close to Takeuchi san, and that's why I have been working with him,
When I received this solo, I thought I could sing here,
So when I received this solo, I thought I could sing here, and I was really moved by it. I was so happy.
I was so happy.
So at the graduation concert, we all went around the perimeter of the Yokohama Arena together in a bright circle,
When I sang that song, it really touched me and filled my heart.
I sang those lyrics, but there were already so many people in the scenery,
I am so glad that I have been able to walk with Mr. Takeuchi this far.
There are so many wonderful lyrics in the song.
Yes, there are. All kinds of lyrics.Please watch the VTR.Here you go!
Presentation of lyrics that touched my heartPresentation of lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, participants will present lyrics from Hello! Project songs that have touched their hearts and talk about their charms.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week I, Nanami Kubota, will be presenting.
Here it is.
This song is called "Don't make fun of me! by Berryz KOBO,
The lyrics are about how indescribably fulfilled I was when my efforts surpassed me,
This is my experience. When I was a trainee at Halo Pro, I practiced for dozens of hours every day to prepare for the proficiency test,
I was practicing for dozens of hours every day for the proficiency test when I was a trainee at Halo Pro. I knew that practicing was not always fun,
I think there were some hardships involved,
However, I had been working hard for the whole year to get a singing award that year,
I was able to win a singing award that year,
When I was able to win the singing award that year, I felt so happy and fulfilled that I was able to forget about the pain I had gone through and the hardships I had gone through,
This song really touched my heart,
So this song really resonated with me, and I thought it could be said for Ochanoma as well,
We are all working very hard at Ochanoma,
For example, when we receive a happy report such as a record award, a newcomer award, or a major label debut,
When we receive such a happy report, for example, a record award, a newcomer award, or a major debut, we feel so fulfilled and happy that it blows away our daily pain, so this song really resonated with me.
It's a really great lyric.
They're really good.
Very good lyrics.
It's hard to come across a time when your efforts exceed your expectations,
And when you meet a time when you can say that it was indescribably fulfilling,
I think this lyric is really destructive.
It really hits home.
It really hits you.
There is a great sense of accomplishment after hard work, isn't there?
I think the lyrics express that kind of feeling,
For example, I think the 10 members of Ochanomizu will overcome many obstacles together,
For example, I think the 10 members of Ochama will overcome many obstacles in the future, and if you listen to this song when you feel like an immortal who has overcome them, you will feel the song once again,
I also felt that I would like to do my best again with the 10 of us.
Yes, it is a very good lyric. The lyrics are very good, so please listen to it.
That's all for now. I hope to do my best again as a group of 10.Hello! Project will celebrate its 25th anniversary in 2023.
This year, 2023, Hello! Project will celebrate its 25th anniversary.
Project 25th Anniversary Concert will be held on September 9 and 10,Project 25th Anniversary Concert will be held on September 9 and 10,
Project 25th Anniversary Concert will be held on September 9 and 10 at the National Yugi Kyogijo Daitaikaikaikan.
Yay! I'm so happy.
It's going to be held for two days.
For two days, over two days.
It's a big event, and there will be gorgeous guests,
We hope to perform as well as the guests.
Yes, I'm sure we will.
Project's 25th anniversary,
Project's 25th anniversary, we would like to introduce some music videos that we have selected from the 25 years of the Project's music videos and would like to focus on the choreography.
I, Akiyama, chose "Be the New Me! by S/mileage.
I first encountered this song at the Hello!
Project trainee presentation, although I didn't perform,
I didn't know much about Hello!
I was surprised and shocked by the choreography and lyrics,
I was surprised by the choreography and the lyrics, and I was also allowed to participate in many of their music videos,
I was also asked to perform in many music videos, and we would go to karaoke parties and dance along with each other,
The choreography was not that difficult, but it was actually very interesting,
The choreography is not that difficult, but when I actually danced it, it was a little difficult,
I really liked the choreography and watched the music video over and over again.
Thank you for watching it!
Miracle is never that big, is it?
Be the new me.
I want to shed my small prejudices and be reborn
Give me more courage
I don't care what anyone thinks of me
Ah...
Hello! Ste!
Next, I, Rikako Sasaki, choose the music video whose choreography I would like to pay attention to,
Doki-Doki Baby by Erina Mano.
I love this song.
I really love this song,
I have already graduated,
Momona Wabara and I once sang this song together on stage, I watched a lot of this music video at that time.
I watched it a lot,Look a lot,
Mano-san was really cute,
I tried my best to live with that poor thing,
And then, this..,
I was so thrilled,
I loved the way he pretended to be excited.
It's so cute.
We made love.
So cute. It was even cuter when Mano-san did it,
I wanted to do it in a cute way too,
I watched a lot of this music video,
I watched a lot of this music video, and the costumes are really cute.
The costumes are really cute, and they look like idol costumes,
I love this music video, and I really love the choreography,
I really love the choreography.
It's a very cute song.
Please watch it.
Maybe Beyond Aniju
Dancing and blowing, blowing
Let's go with the wind
Flash your light
I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it.
I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you
Shalala lala lala lala lala Feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it in your heart
Heart pounding, heart pounding baby
Dokidoki doki doki baby
Subtitle: Kiyohiroi ne
Let's do our best tomorrow!
Rikako Sasaki of Angulum and Maasa Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory present "Halo! Sta.
It's time to say goodbye. Here's an announcement.
Hello Project 2023 Summer City Circuit is now underway.
Angelem will be performing in Aichi on Saturday the 19th and Tsubaki Factory on Sunday the 20th.
We have a few days left to go, but we will all make it through to the end.
Tsubaki Factory will perform at Uppity Presents Shine Fest 2023 on August 19. And on Thursday, August 24, we will be holding Tsubaki Factory's Summer Festival 2023 Scorching Heat.
We are really working hard as one for this concert, so I hope you are looking forward to it.We are really working as one for this concert, and I hope you are looking forward to it.
On August 26, we will be performing at the At Jamun Expo 2023 Supported by Uptee.
Since it is already summer, I will do my best to train my muscles every day so that I will not lose my stamina for the event.
Angelem is going on an autumn concert tour from May 16th.
New members will be joining the group in earnest from the fall tour, so please look forward to it.
Tsubaki Factory is also going on an autumn tour.
I don't know what songs we will sing yet, but I will do my best to entertain everyone who comes to the concert.
And on September 27, we will be releasing a triple A-side single, "Courage! It's my life! If you're just delusional, you can be free! It's my life!
It's my life!" The songs are all different genres, so I am sure you will find a song that you like.
I am also going to have overseas concerts in Hong Kong and Taiwan.
This is the first time for me to go abroad, so I am very excited to see what I can do and what kind of audience I will have.
Project 25th Anniversary concert will be held on September 9 and 10.
Project 25th Anniversary concert will be held on Saturday and Sunday, September 9 and 10, and all of the current members, including OG members, will perform.
Let's make it a festival-like 2 days!
The "Hello! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
Project members. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time we have Rikako Sasaki of Angulum and Maasa Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory.
Farewell!
undefined